In the same way, we can make a flower cover
for the back of the chicken.
We'll make a flower cover
The back of the chicken can't be used
as the chair and the floor material.
Then hide the unused objects
Because the model is placed neatly, it can be used to make a backrest version of the image in the 2D window
Also use the positioning tool to locate the backrest model
Adjust the four corners
Hide the backrest model
Use the positioning tool to locate the backrest model
Because we need to make a backrest model, we need to create some inner circles first
Press the CTRL key to center the model
Press the SHIFT key to center the model
Then copy and paste the inner circle
You can place the inner circle according to your preference
After that, make a backrest model
It is also suitable to make a backrest model similar to the previous one
Because we have used the backrest layer function before,
The inner circle has automatically generated the backrest line
To improve the effect, you can hide the outer panel
Select the inner backrest model to reduce the conflict thickness
Then paste it on the backrest model
After simulation, the pressure of the outer layer will be increased to 10 to create the effect of inflating the cotton.
It can be seen that because the inner circle is sewed together, it will not swell due to the inflating of the inner circle.
After selecting the outer layer and hiding it, add the fixing pin to the inner circle position.
Then select all the fixing pins at the same time, and select to fix them to the virtual model.
After selecting this function, the fixing pin will be fixed to its original position.
The fixing pin will be fixed to the closest model.
However, sometimes the fixing pin is too close to the model, and it will be attached to it.
You can manually delete these fixing pins, or move to the right position and attach it to the virtual model.
Then you can see that because the fixing pin is attached to the model, the seam will be deeper.
Before you remove the fixing pin, you can manually add the sewing pin to the machine, and move to the inside of the mobile version.
After all, you can see the fixing pin is attached to theこれpon to press the permission button.
If you want to have a more obvious fold, you can choose all internal lines to apply elasticity.
If you shrink the elasticity value a little, you will have a very obvious fold effect.
There will be more and more obvious folds after reducing the粒子間距.
Changes in the angle of the foot can make the folds more sharp, obvious, or softer and rounder.
The smaller the angle of the foot, the softer it looks.
The higher the angle of the foot, the harder it looks.
In addition, if you reduce the elastic ratio of the circle, you will also have an obvious fold effect.
Hide the outside layers of the seat, so that you can choose the inner model, and then the model that is anti-activated before activation.
Then display the outside seats and activate them.
Turn on the simulation and let the panels interact.
Hide the side panels and select the inner model.
Use the positioning ball to drag the inner model.
The outer fabric will move together.
Slow down the movement as much as possible during the movement process to avoid stretching too fast and not penetrating.
Press Shift W to display all panels.